<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lee-or Alon</title>
    <link>https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lee-or Alon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Lee-or Alon</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:49:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Forum of PhD Students at BIU</title>
      <link>https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/ourforum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:49:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/ourforum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am very proud to announce the first meeting of The Forum of PhD Students at Bar-Ilan University.
&lt;/br&gt;
Bar-Ilan&amp;rsquo;s PhD students represent the future of research and the Israeli academic community. Building connections with our peers is crucial for fostering successful collaborations and driving groundbreaking research initiatives.
Throughout our academic journeys, we encounter similar challenges, including navigating mentorship dynamics, balancing work with daily life commitments, managing research schedules, grappling with research roadblocks, and facing the disappointment of conference rejections, among others. However, most of us don&amp;rsquo;t know the PhD students who sit down the hall, let alone those in other faculties.
The main goal of this forum is to address that absurd situation. It not only equips PhD students with tools to enhance their research skills but also acts as a platform for sharing experiences, mutual consultation, and fostering collaborations. By providing an informal setting, the forum offers students the chance to interact, deepen their connections, and engage in discussions on shared interests.
&lt;/br&gt;
Interested in joining? Contact me 😊&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/view/ourforum&#34; 
target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[The Forum of PhD Students at BIU University]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women CS Circle</title>
      <link>https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/women_cs_circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:49:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee-oralon.github.io/post/women_cs_circle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a CS student at Bar Ilan University?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If so, check out this group 🎓&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/groups/367083367959151?ref=share&amp;mibextid=DcJ9fc&#34; 
target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[Women CS Circle]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
